http://interbird.com/company/privacy.html

InterBird.com
Privacy policy
Introduction
Interbird Inc (Interbird/we/us) is giving the top priority to protecting your privacy and personal information. This privacy policy explains what personal information we collect and how we use that information. We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. When the policy changes, you'll see a notification on our website
By using the Site, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to our collection, use, disclosure and retention of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. You also consent to the use of cookies, beacons and information by us and by the third parties mentioned in this privacy policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.
1. Purpose of data processing
We collect and process personal data for the following purposes:
To provide the services you require on our website.
To improve our website and service.
To ensure the security of our website.
To sign you up for our membership (manufacturer only)
To help our advertising effort, using anonymous personal data
We use your data only in accordance with this privacy policy that you have consented.
2. Data collected
When you visit our website or use our service, information about your visit, such as your browser type, your IP address, the page served are passively collected by our system. The collection may be implemented by third parties or our partners. This information is generally collected using the web cookies, hyperlinks that contain web or pixels (beacons). You can set your browser to disable or delete those cookies. The following are types of cookies and its purpose. We do not use the collected information to identify you without your consent. Below are the type of cookies we collect.
Functionality Cookies
Functionality Cookies allow our website to remember the choices you make, such as your login information (if any), preferred language or region you are in, and can provide enhanced, more personal features. These Cookies can also be used to remember changes you made to text size, fonts and other parts of Sites pages you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these Cookies collect may be anonymized, and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these Cookies on your device.
Advertising Cookies
These Cookies collect information to deliver you more relevant advertising. They may be placed by us, by third parties acting on our behalf, or by advertising networks with our permission. They remember other websites you have visited, and advertising networks may share this information with others including advertisers. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these Cookies on your device.
Performance Cookies
Performance Cookies collect anonymized information about how you use the Sites. For example, these Cookies may tell us which pages you go to most often and if you receive error messages from our web pages. We use this information to improve how our Sites work. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these cookies on your device.
3. Types of data collected
“Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like names, addresses, e-mail addresses, or phone numbers, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. We only collect your personal information when you provide it to us by contacting us.
“Anonymous Information” means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons.
4. Recipients of the data
We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. We will do not share your personal information except as specified in this Privacy Policy. We use third party data processors to process personal data on our behalf. These service providers specifically support us for hosting, operating, marketing, analyzing for our website improvement. This processor can be a non-European location. The processing of data collected this way is governed by the privacy policies of each platform.
Our content may be linked to third party websites and can provide relevant references. We are not responsible for external content that may include other privacy policies and data processing disclosures. We may disclose your personal information if required by law, regulation, or other legal subpoena or warrant. We may disclose personal information to regulatory agencies and law enforcement agencies if we believe that we need to protect the rights of customers or third parties, property or personal safety.
5. Communication
If you send us email for communication and other purposes, we use your personal information to contact you. You may withdraw or refuse our contact at any time by clicking on the opt-out function or by sending e-mail us.
6. Data protection
We take proper measures to protect the collected information from abuse and loss. We keep these data in a secure environment. The data processed for any purpose(s) will not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose.
We regularly educate our employees about data protection. While we make the best & reasonable efforts to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data transmitted through our website.
7. Rights and Contact Information
If you have a request, the Data Protection Officer will provide you with your information we store about you. If your personal information is inaccurate, you have the right to correct or delete it. You may revoke your consent to use your personal information in whole or in part or to remove personal information in the future.
Please contact our Data Protection Officer for any requests, questions or comments regarding the handling of this privacy policy.
Data protection officer
Nak Bok Sung
E-Mail: Privacy@interbird.com
